ingenioso.tv 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy - Ingenioso

**What information do we collect?** We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. **What do we use your information for?** Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. **How do we protect your information?** We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. **Do we use cookies?** Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. **Google Direct Advertising** We have implemented several Google Analytics features which are based on Display Advertising, specifically Remarketing and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting. You may opt-out of these services by visiting your Google [ads settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). **Google Remarketing**

  * We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.
  * Ingenioso and other third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to our website.

**Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting**

  * We collect and use data from Google’s demographic reporting (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics. We use this data privately for better displaying more targeted site content as well as ad content.

**Third party links** Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance** Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and editing their profile by clicking on their username. **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance** We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. **Online Privacy Policy Only** This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. **Terms and Conditions** Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [by clicking here](http://www.ingenioso.tv/terms-and-conditions) **Your Consent** By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. **Changes to our Privacy Policy** If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date at the top of this page. For any further information please email contact@ingenioso.tv Ingenioso http://www.ingenioso.tv  

Close

Please support our site

Please Like us to get daily updates on Facebook
